你的第一次性经验  是跟女人在一起
So, uh, your first sexual experience was with a woman?
好吧  当时我十五岁  对方是我的好朋友鲁丝
All right, I was 15. It was my best friend, Ruth...
我们喝苹果酒喝醉了
...and we got drunk on that hard cider.
我不知道  突然间我们开始亲热
And then suddenly, I don't know, we were making out.
再说一次
Tell it again.
真的
Seriously.
那个女人除了性  还会说别的事吗
Is that woman capable of talking about anything else but sex?
当然  之前她提到地理
Yeah, sure. Well, you know, earlier, she was talking about geography.
乔伊  她是在说她做过的国家
Joey, she was listing the countries she's done it in.
我想我们都学会一些事
Well, I think we all learned something.
各位  看看我发现了什么  看看这个
Hey, you guys. Look what I found. Look at this.
那是我妈的笔迹  看吧
That's my mom's writing. Look.
"我  法兰克跟菲比的毕业典礼  1965年"
"Me and Frank and Phoebe, graduation, 1965."
你们知道那是什么意思吗  你已经五十岁了
Do you know what that means? That you're actually 50?
不  那不是我  那是她的朋友菲比
No, no. That's not "me" Phoebe. That's her pal, Phoebe.
根据她的高中毕业纪念册  她们是BFF
According to her high school yearbook, they were BFF.
永远的好朋友
Best friends forever. BOTH Oh.
真的很棒  太酷了
That's great. That is so cool.
所以这女人可能…
I know. So this woman probably could...
她知道我爸妈的故事
Like, has all kinds of stories about my parents.
或许她知道我爸在哪里
And she might even know where my dad is.
我查了一下资料  发现她住在海滩
So I looked her up and she lives by the beach.
或许这个周末  我们可以到海滩去
So maybe this weekend we can go to the beach.
当然可以  对
Yeah, we can. Yeah.
该死  我不能去  我得上班  太糟糕了
Shoot, I can't go. I have to work. That's too bad.
糟透了
Aw, big fat bummer.
太棒了  明天我们开车到蒙托克
So great. Okay, tomorrow we're gonna drive out to Montauk.
邦妮在那里做过
Hey, Bonnie had sex there.
《老友记》 第三季 第25集  海滩之旅
Friends S03E25  The One at the Beach
（主演：詹妮弗·安妮斯顿）
（主演：柯特妮·考克斯）
（主演：丽莎·库卓）
（主演：马特·勒布朗）
（主演：马修·派瑞）
（主演：大卫·修蒙）
（中央咖啡厅）
你看看他们
Would you look at them?
我再也交不到男朋友了
I'm never gonna find a boyfriend again.
我得当一辈子的老处女
I'm gonna die an old maid.
你不会当一辈子的老处女
You're not gonna die an old maid.
比较可能的是老处女厨师
Maybe an old spinster cook.
谢了  而且如果真的没希望了
Thanks. Hey, besides, worse comes to worse...
我可以当你的男朋友
...I'll be your boyfriend. Ha-ha-ha.
对啊
Yeah, right.
有什么好笑的
Why is that so funny?
你是在开玩笑  对吧
You made a joke, right?
所以我笑了
So I laughed.
你笑得太用力了
A little too hard.
怎么  我不适合当男朋友吗
What, am I not, uh, boyfriend material?
不  你是钱德
No. You're Chandler.
你知道的  钱德
You know. Chandler.
好吧  我们确定我的名字  还打了我
Okay, so we've established my name, and hit me.
如果我们不认识   是别人介绍的
But theoretically, say we weren't friends. Say it's a blind date.
我跑到你家门口这么说
I show up at your door and I'm, like, uh:
"嘿  幸会…"
"Hey,nice to meet you."
或许我会怕用假声说话的男人
I'd probably be scared of a guy using a fake voice.
嘿  太好了  你买了吃的
JHey. Oh, hey. Oh, good. You bought food.
不  这是我的行李
No, just my luggage.
大家好
Hey. ey, guys.
好了  太棒了
All right. Yeah.
这星期我运气不错
Oh, I am having the best karma this week.
先是找到这个认识我爸妈的女人
First, I find this woman who knew my parents...
然后长了背毛的客人  把他的海滩小屋借我用
...and then my client with the fuzzy back gives me his beach house.
那个被你打的快递员呢
What about that, uh, bike messenger you hit?
我又不是在说他的运气
Oh, I wasn't talking about his karma.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
看看那顶帽子
Hey, check out the hat.
等一下  我认得那顶帽子
Wait a minute, I know that hat.
我被绑架到那顶帽子里（UFO）
I was taken aboard that hat.
他们对我做实验
They did experiments on me.
我生不出孩子了
I can't have children.
说真的  你去哪里买那顶帽子的
Seriously, where did you get the hat?
是罗斯送我的
Ross gave it to me.
我想她很漂亮  谢谢
Aw, I think she looks good. Thank you.
他为你买了帽子
Did he buy it for you...
或为你赢了帽子
...or win it for you?
对不起  我的时尚白痴朋友们
Well, excuse me, my fashion-impaired friends...
我得告诉你们  帽子又开始流行起来了
...I'm here to tell you that hats are back.
这次它们成群结队  组成庞大的超级大帽子
And this time, they've ganged up and formed one giant super-hat.
快点
Go, go, go.
现在大家都想躲在帽子下面
Now everybody wants to be under the hat.
为什么满地都是沙子
What's with all this sand?
对  巴伯说过地板可能坏了
Oh, yeah. Bob said there might be flood damage.
不然就是他养了一只超大的猫
Either that or he has a really big cat.
对  那栋房子非常特别
Well, yes, it's kind of an unusual house.
它有三间漂亮的卧室  没有浴室
It has, um, three beautiful bedrooms and, uh, no baths.
但大海就在旁边
But, you know, the ocean is right there.
有人在吗
Knock, knock, knock.
稍等一下  请进
Hang on a second. Come in, come in.
考虑一下  再回我电话吧
All right, so think about it and call me back.
你是菲比艾波特吗  对
Are you Phoebe Abbott? Uh, yes.
大惊喜  菲比艾波特  我是你好朋友的女儿
Surprise, Phoebe Abbott. I'm your best friend's daughter.
你是厄文的女儿
You're Irwin's daughter?
我知道  我是指你以前的好朋友  看吧
I know. I mean, your old best friend. Here.
莉莉  高中同学  记得吗  天啊  莉莉  对
Lily? From high school? Remember? Oh, God. Lily. Yes.
我当然记得莉莉
Of course I remember Lily.
我…那么你一定是…
I... Then you must be...
菲比  菲比
Phoebe, Phoebe.
菲比  对  我想她以你的名字帮我命名
Phoebe, yeah. She named me after you, I guess.
看吧  那是法兰克
Uh-huh. Wow. Well. Look, there's Frank.
没错
Yeah. Yes. Yes, yes.
他是我爸   他是法兰克
That's my dad. That's Frank. Ha, ha. Oh!
抱歉我这么激动
I'm sorry I'm getting all flingy. Oh!
冷静点  如果你要的话  梳理台有饼干
Take it easy. If you want, there's cookies on the counter.
或水果酒  我能调些水果酒  不
Or sangria. I could make sangria. No, no.
抱歉  饼干就可以了  谢谢
Sorry. Cookies are good, thanks. Oh.
总之我一直在找我爸
So, um, anyway, um, I've been looking for my father and, um...
你有他的消息或看过他吗  不  对不起
Have you heard from him or seen him? Oh, no, I'm sorry.
高中毕业后  我就没有跟任何人联络了
I guess I lost track of everybody after high school.
好吧
Okay.
跟我说说我爸妈的事  什么事都可以
Well, so tell me everything about my parents. Everything.
你知道的  我们老是粘在一起
Oh, well, you know, we were always together.
其他孩子帮我们取了绰号
The other kids had a nickname for the three of us.
什么绰号  三个失败者
Oh, what? What was it? The Three Losers.
可怜的莉莉
Oh, poor Lily.
我听说她的事了  你一定非常难过
You know, I heard about what happened. That must have been just terrible for you...
就这样失去了母亲
...losing your mother that way.
不  那是件好事
Yeah, no, it was great.
你们知道雨天最适合玩什么吗
You know what a really good rainy-day game is?
什么  我是指裸体游戏
What? I mean, naked game.
脱衣扑克牌  我们应该玩脱衣扑克牌
Strip poker. We should play strip poker.
不  你疯了吗
No. Are you crazy?
来吧  度假就得疯狂玩一场   那就像是  法律
Come on. When you go away, you have to play. It's, like, a law.
好了  谢谢
All done. Aw, thank you.
好吧   接下来轮到谁了
Okay. Who's next?
不要
No.
绝对不行
No way.
来吧  拜托  我好无聊  之前你让我这么做过
Come on, please. I'm bored. You let me do it once before.
对   如果那是本周末的规则
Yeah, well, if, uh... If that's the rule this weekend...
走开  像男子汉一样  罗斯  来吧
Get away. Take it like a man, Ross. Come on.
不要 来吧
No, no. Oh, come on.
大恶霸
Big bullies.
不…
No, no, no.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
大家还好吧
Oh. So how are we doing?
超无聊的
Bored and bored.
你们知道什么样的裸体牌局  一点都不无聊吗
Hey, you know what naked card game's never boring?
不行
No.
菲比是什么样的人
So, what's Phoebe like?
我仁慈   有爱心又可爱  摩妮卡是什么样的人
I'm kind, caring and sweet. What's Monica like? Ha, ha.
不  另一个菲比  你去找的那个女人
Uh, no, the other Phoebe. The one you went to see?
喔  我想她知道我爸在哪里
Oh, I think she knows where my dad is.
什么   酷啊
What? Cool.
他在哪里
Well, where is he?
她假装多年来没有跟他联络
She was pretending like she hasn't heard from him in years...
不过  我在她的冰箱上发现这张照片
...but I found this picture on her fridge.
看吧  他现在应该长这个样子对吧
Look, isn't this what he would look like now?
真的好像  对
Totally familiar. Yeah.
对  对
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
为什么她要骗你
Why would she lie to you?
我不知道  我们今晚要一起吃晚饭
I don't know, but we're having dinner tomorrow.
我想她会告诉我
I figured she's gonna tell me then.
或许她要给他时间
You know, maybe she just wanted to give him time...
买礼物送我  我不知道
...to buy me presents. I don't know. Ha, ha.
你们都很无聊  对
So you're all bored? Yes.
好吧  我要闭上眼睛  指着某个人
All right, I'm gonna close my eyes and point to someone.
被我指到的人得想出有趣的点子   大家都得那么做
And whoever I point to has to come up with something fun to do. And we have to do it.
好吧  散开  好吧
Okay. All right. Fan out. Fan out. Okay.
好吧
Okay.
我们可以一直这么做
Ooh, you know, we could just do this.
好吧
Okay, um...
我们都得玩脱衣扑克牌
We all have to play strip poker?
太棒了
Oh, yes!
脱衣大富翁游戏
Strip Happy Days game?
我找不到牌  不玩这个
Yeah, well, I couldn't find any cards, so it was either this...
我们就得玩脱衣打毛线游戏
...or Strip Bag-of-Old-Knitting-Stuff.
好吧
Done.
Okay.
"方兹给你竖起两根拇指  你可以拿到两分"
"Fonzie gives you two thumbs up. Collect two cool points."
对  对
Yeah. Yeah.
拿到五分  你可以要某人脱掉一件衣服
Get five cool points, you get to make someone take off one item of clothing.
还没有人开始脱  我们都非常兴奋
It hasn't happened yet, but we're all very excited.
好了  来吧
Okay, come on.
我需要新电磁显微镜
Daddy needs a new pair of electromagnetic microscopes...
送给史前监识部门
...for the Prehistoric Forensics department.
好吧  "带粉红托斯卡迪洛  到冥想地点"
Okay. "Take Pinky Tuscadero up to Inspiration Point.
"你可以拿到三分"  太棒了
Collect three cool points." Yeah.
所以我拿到五分了
Which gives me five.
让我想一想   谁得脱掉衣服
And let's see, who is gonna lose their clothes?
我想挑脱衣扑克牌赞助商  乔伊崔比亚尼先生
Um, I think I pick our strip poker sponsor, Mr. Joey Tribbiani.
好吧   放轻松  只是一只鞋子
All right, relax. It's just a shoe.
"你的乐团在阿诺家表演  你可以拿到三分"
"Your band is playing at Arnold's. Collect three cool points."
也就是说  我有五分了  我要乔伊脱掉内裤
Which means I have five, and that means I get Joey's boxers.
好吧  你们联手欺负我
Fine. Gang up on me.
我会让你们脱得很难看
I got you all right where I want you.
来吧  快脱
Come on. Take them off.
好吧  现在好冷的
Actually, you know, it's kind of cold.
我能不能继续穿着内裤  让你们可以看一眼我的宝贝
So how about I keep my boxers on and give you all a peek at the good stuff?
好吧  我要再去调玛格丽特
All right, I'm gonna make more margaritas.
你在做什么  你要灌醉我吗
Whoa, hey, what are you doing? Trying to get me drunk?
我只是要调玛格丽特
I'm just making margaritas.
我去帮她
Think I'll help her out.
发生了什么事  什么
What is going on here? What?
你帮他的脚趾涂指甲油  少来了
You're painting his toenails. Oh, come on.
追着他满屋子跑  摩妮卡  拜托
Chasing him around the room. Monica, please.
他也跟你眉来眼去的
He's totally flirting with you too.
他真的那么做  是吧
He is, isn't he?
我不知道  或许是因为我们一起来海滩
I don't know. I don't know. Maybe it's just being here at the beach together...
但那像是…
...or but it's like something...
嘿
Hey.
嗨  邦妮  嗨
Hi, Bonnie. Hi.
老板让我提早下班   我搭火车过来了
My boss let me off early, so I took the train.
你们在做什么
Oh. What are you guys doing?
我们在玩脱衣大富翁
We're playing Strip Happy Days game.
酷啊  我来赶进度
Cool. I'll catch up.
你还是不觉得
So you still don't think...
我能当你的男朋友
...I'm boyfriend material?
昨晚玩牌时你一直盯着我看
Saw you checking me out during the game last night.
你连裤子都没脱  对  你很幸运
You didn't even take off your pants. Yeah, well, lucky for you.
什么   我不知道
What? I don't know.
其他人都玩得很开心吗
Well, is everybody else having just the best time?
乔伊在睡觉
Joey's asleep.
他昏睡过去  我们帮他铺上沙子保暖
After he passed out, we put sand around him to keep him warm.
我想那对幸福情侣还没起床吧
Well, I assume the, uh, happy couple isn't up yet?
昨晚有听到他们的声音吗
Did you guys hear them last night?
有   我不知道他们在做什么
Oh, yeah. I don't know what they were doing...
但海龟真的爬进屋里了
...but sea turtles actually came up to the house.
早安
Good morning. Hey.
大家睡得还好吧   非常棒
How'd everybody sleep? Great.
睡得很熟
Like a log.
我们也是  我们也是
Us too.
我要去散步
I'm going for a walk.
早安  好丰满的胸部
Good morning. Nice breasts, by the way.
你是怎么了
Hey, what happened to you?
没事   我只是想坐在这里看书
Oh, uh, nothing. I just felt like hanging out here and reading.
海水太舒服了
Oh, the water was so great.
我们一跳下码头   我的泳衣就掉了
We jumped off this pier and my suit came off.
可惜我没看到
Oh. Sorry I missed that.
乔伊跟钱德太好笑了
Joey and Chandler sure are funny.
我的头发里都是沙子
I think I brought back half the beach in my hair.
以前剃光头就没这么麻烦
It was so much easier when I used to shave my head.
知道吗  我得跟你说
You know, I gotta tell you...
我喜欢你光头的造型
...I just loved your look when you were bald.
真的
Really? Oh.
因为我一直在想  要再剃光头
Because I think about shaving it all off again sometimes.
真的吗  对
Really? Yeah.
我是说你该那么做
I mean, you definitely should do that.
你知道吗  我该这么做的  对
You know what? I should do it. Yeah.
你知道吗  谢谢你  瑞秋  你太酷了
You know what? Thank you, Rachel. You are so cool.
别说了  去吧
Oh, stop. Go on.
快去剃光头吧  好的
Now, go shave that head.All right.
怎么了  菲比
What's the matter, Pheebs?
她取消约会  那个女人取消跟我的约会
She canceled. My namesake canceled on me.
什么  她说她有急事要出城
What? She claims she had to go out of town.
她在躲我
She's avoiding me.
她不想说我爸的下落  她知道  但她就不肯告诉我
She doesn't want to tell me where my father is. She knows and she won't tell.
菲比  那样做真差劲
Aw, Pheebs, that sucks.
对  我不想再差劲下去了
Yeah, well, don't "Aw, Pheebs, that sucks" me yet.
你要去哪里  她出城去了
Where are you going? Well, she's out of town.
她家里应该会有我爸下落的线索
So there's gotta be something in her house that tells me where my father is.
菲比  有人会说那是非法侵入
Uh, Pheebs, some people call that "breaking and entering."
你们是那么想的吗   没有
Well, are any of those people here? Oh, no.
听着  我会做好事弥补  好吗
Okay. Look, I'll do something nice, okay?
我会帮她装满制冰盒  好吗
I'll fill her ice trays. Good?
大家好
Hey, everybody.
看看你做了什么
Ha, look what you did.
你要摸摸看吗  不  但那真的很好看
You wanna touch it? No, but it's great.
来吧  摸摸看
Come on, touch it.
好吧
Okay.
可以感觉到你的头  全部都是骨头
You can feel all the bones in your skull.
嗨  嗨
Hi. Hi.
我跟邦妮聊过  你猜怎么了
I was having a little chat with Bonnie, and, uh, guess what.
她不经意提起
She happened to bring up, you know...
是谁唆使她剃光头发的
...who was behind the whole, um, head-shaving idea.
到底是谁呢  没错  就是你
And now, who was it? Oh, that's right. That's right, it was you.
那是她的点子
That was her idea.
我只是推了她一把
I just gave her a nudge.
她说是你给她刮胡刀片的
She said you gave her the razor.
嘿  嘿
Yo. Hey.
有人要到海里来场夜泳吗
So anyone up for a midnight dip in the ocean?
我不要  谢谢  不不
Uh, no, I'm good. RACHEL: No, thanks.
好吧  待会见  好好玩  再见
Okay, I'll see you in a bit. Okay, have fun. Bye.
少来了  看吧  她看起来没那么糟糕
Come on, see? She doesn't look that bad.
你可以看到她的头反射月光
You can see the moonlight bouncing off her head.
你到底在想什么  我不知道
What the hell were you thinking? I don't know.
你不知道  瑞秋  你害我女朋友变成光头
You don't know? Rach, you balded my girlfriend.
好吧  罗斯
All right. Ross.
你以为我很开心  看到你跟别人在一起吗
Do you think it's easy for me to see you with somebody else?
你知道吗  是你跟我分手的
You know what? You're the one who ended it.
对  因为我生你的气  不是因为我不再爱你了
Yeah, because I was mad at you. Not because I stopped loving you.
你还爱我吗  没有
You still love me? No.
你还爱我
You still love me.
对  所以呢  你爱我
Yeah, so? You love me.
没…
No... Mm.
这是什么意思  你想…
What does this mean? What do you...?
你想跟我复合吗
I mean, do you want to get back together?
不   或许吧
No. Maybe.
我不知道
I don't know.
罗斯
Ross...
我还是无法原谅你做了那件事
I still can't forgive you for what you did.
我只是…有时候我跟你在一起  我觉得…
I just... But sometimes when I'm with you, I just feel so...
什么
What?
我觉得…
I just... I feel...
我… 什么
I just... What?
我觉得…
I feel...
不   我不在乎
No. I don't care.
我不跟你  玩一对一脱衣扑克牌来练习了
I'm not playing one-on-one strip poker with you for practice.
我做了扑克牌
But I made cards.
好吧
Well.
晚安
Good night.
我要上楼了
I'm going upstairs.
晚安 晚安
Good night. Night.
要玩脱衣扑克牌当做练习吗
Wanna play strip poker for practice?
我的屁股
My ass.
好吧
Okay.
Okay, good.
不   是我
Aah! No! Oh, it's me. It's me.
我不想发出声音  那就不要闯进来
I didn't wanna make any noise. Then don't break in.
对不起  你来这做什么
I'm sorry. What are you doing here?
我来帮你装制冰盒
I came to fill your ice-cube tray.
什么
What?
好吧
Um, okay.
好吧   听我说
Okay, look. Huh. Ahem.
我从你的冰箱拿走这张照片  因为我知道他是我爸
I took this picture from your fridge, okay? Because I know that this is my father.
对  他是法兰克布非  你就站在他旁边
Yeah, this is Frank Buffay, and you were standing right there next to him.
听着  我有资格知道我的出身
Now, look, I deserve to know where I came from.
好吗  如果你能帮我找到我爸  你该那么做
All right? So if you can help me find my father, then you should.
不然你就是个坏人
Otherwise, you're just mean.
告诉我真相
So just tell me the truth.
好吧
All right.
照片里的男人是查克曼吉诺尼
The man in that picture is Chuck Mangione.
我爸是查克曼吉诺尼
My father is Chuck Mangione?
不   他只是查克曼吉诺尼
No, no. That's just Chuck Mangione.
去年我卖房子给他
I sold him a house last year.
我很抱歉  但我真的不知道你爸在哪里
And I'm very sorry, but I really don't know where your father is.
真的
And that's the truth.
不过你说的对
But, um, you're right.
我想人都该知道自己的出身
I think that a person should know where they come from.
所以我…
Which is why I, uh...
好吧
Okay...
我是你妈
I'm your mother.
昨天我想告诉你   可是我…
You know, I wanted to tell you yesterday, but I just...
我不是很想说  而且…
I felt all floopy, and...
我是认真的   你们应该复合
I'm telling you. You guys are getting back together.
才怪   她甚至不知道她要什么
That's not true. She doesn't even know what she wants.
瑞秋还在为那件事生气
Rachel's still mad about the whole thing.
好吧  那么你应该放手  你不需要那样受伤害
Okay, well, then you gotta back away. You don't need that kind of hurt.
相信我的话   我…
Take it from a guy who's...
从来没有长时间跟女人交往过
...never had a long-term relationship.
我知道  但我真的很想  跟她完成那个吻
I know, but I really want to go up there and finish that kiss.
嘿
Hey. Aah.
各位  海水太棒了  你们该去游个泳
You guys, the water is great. You should really go in.
不用了  谢谢  我刚吃了巧克力
Oh, uh, no, thanks. I just had an M&M.
好吧  晚安
Okay. Well, good night.
晚安
ROSS: Good night.
快点回房  好的
Don't be too long. Okey-dokey.
她头上一根毛都没有
There is not one hair on that head.
她的头发会长回来的  好吗  而且她既风趣又酷
Hey, it'll grow back, right? And she's really fun, and she's cool.
我终于有了新生活
And I'm finally moving on.
我是说要忘记瑞秋  真的  你们知道吗
I mean, getting over Rachel was so, ugh, you know?
我终于又恢复了理智   如果我现在上楼
You know, I'm finally feeling sane again. And now if I go up there...
吻了她…
...and I kiss her and...
天啊  我真的好想吻她
God, I want to kiss her.
那要是失败了呢  好吗
And it doesn't work out, right?
我真的要让自己再受一次苦吗
Do I really wanna put myself through that again?
我得把事情弄清楚
So let me get this straight.
如果今晚你去找邦妮
If you go with Bonnie tonight...
你做了聪明正确的选择  继续过你的新生活
...you're doing the smart, healthy thing and moving on.
对  好吗
Yeah. Right?
如果去找瑞秋  今晚邦妮就有空了
And if you go with Rachel, Bonnie's free tonight?
嗨
Hi.
你好
Hi there.
你又装怪声了
That's that weird voice again.
好吧   让我再试一次
Let me try it again.
我发誓你会想跟我约会的  好了  来吧
You're gonna wanna date this next guy, I swear. Okay, come on.
嗨  我是小矮人
Hi, I'm Dorf.
你今晚的男伴
Your date for the evening.
别这样  跟小矮人约会  很好玩耶
Oh, come on. Dorf on dating? That's good stuff.